BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 9012, 1992-2004 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  1/1992 - 7/1993; 5/1996; 5/1996 - 5/1999; 5/1999 - 5/2004
- 800000, 2001-2003 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  6/2001; 12/2003
- 800007, 1996-2004 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  6/1996; 6/2002; 6/2004
- 800009, 1993-2007 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  6/1993; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800009, 1991-1999 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  7/1991 - 6/1993; 7/1996 - 6/1999
- 800013, 2003-2009 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  6/2009; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800020, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  7/2006
- 800027, 1979-1996 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  12/1979; 12/1982; 12/1983; 12/1986; 6/1996
- 800027, 1999-2007 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  6/1999; 6/2002; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800033, 1993-2006 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  6/1993; 12/1999; 6/2002; 6/2006
- 800038, 1999-2007 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  4/1999; 4/2003; 4/2007
- 800038, 1972-1985 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  4/1972 - 3/1985
- 800039, 1995-2007 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2007; 6/2007
- 800050, 1999-2006 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  10/1999; 12/2002; 6/2006
- 800056, 1976-1999 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  6/1976; 12/1980; 12/1983; 12/1986; 12/1993; 10/1999
- 800062, 1995-2007 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  4/1995; 4/1999; 4/2003; 4/2007
- 800064, 1994-2005 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  6/1994; 6/1997; 8/2001; 7/2005
- 800065, 1995-2001 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  10/1995; 10/1998; 10/2001
- 800077, 1991-2003 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  6/1991; 6/1993; 6/1995; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2003
- 800077, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  6/2005
- 800077, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  6/2001
- 800087, 1991-2007 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  3/1991; 4/1999; 4/2003; 4/2007
- 800096, 1995-2007 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800096, 1992-1999 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  7/1992 - 6/1999
- 800097, 2005-2007 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  6/2005; 6/2007
- 800097, 1997-2003 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  3/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800097, 1989-1997 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  7/1989 - 6/1991; 7/1995 - 6/1997
- 800098, 1995-2007 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  3/1995; 4/1999; 4/2003; 4/2007
- 800099, 1999-2003 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  4/1999; 4/2003 (extension)
- 800100, 1997-2005 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  7/1997; 7/2000; 7/2005
- 800101, 1995-2002 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  6/1995; 6/2000; 9/2002
- 800102, 1994-2002 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  12/1994; 12/1999; 3/31/2002
- 800103, 1999-2007 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  6/1999; 6/2002; 6/2007
- 800104, 1996-2006 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  10/1996; 10/1997; 10/1999; 10/2002; 10/2004; 10/2006
- 800105, 1997-2007 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  6/1997; 6/2000; 6/2003; 12/2007
- 800106, 1999-2005 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  6/1999; 6/2002; 6/2005
- 800107, 1999-2005 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  6/1999; 6/2000; 6/2005
- 800108, 1997-2003 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  9/1997; 9/2000; 9/2001; 9/2003
- 800109, 1997-2006 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  6/1997; 6/1998; 6/2000; 6/2006
- 800110, 1998-2002 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  6/1998; 6/1999; 6/2002
- 800111, 1998-2004 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  9/1998; 9/2001; 9/2004
- 800112, 1996-2005 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  8/1996; 8/1997; 10/1998; Evergreen (2/1999); 8/1/2002; 8/2005
- 800113, 1997-2003 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  8/1997; 8/2001; 8/2003
- 800114, 1999-2005 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  8/1999; 8/2002; 8/2005
- 800115, 1998-2006 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  8/1998; 8/2000; 8/2002; 8/2003; 8/2006
- 800116, 1998-2008 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  8/1998; 8/2001; 8/2004; 8/2008
- 800117, 2002-2006 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  8/2002; 8/2003; 8/2006
- 800118, 1998-2005 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  8/1998; 8/2000; 8/2003; 8/2005
- 800119, 1997-2001 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  6/1997; 6/2000; 6/2001
- 800122, 1986-1999 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  6/1986; 6/1989; 6/1993; 6/1999
- 800136, 2001-2007 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  6/2007; 6/2001; 6/2004
- 800137, 1998-2004 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  6/1998; 6/2001; 6/2004
- 800138, 1977-2003 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  3/1977; 3/1982; 3/1985; 3/1988; 3/1991; 4/1999; 3/2003
- 800139, 1995-2003 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  4/1995; 4/1999; 3/2003
- 800140, 1999-2008 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  6/1999; 6/2002; 6/2004; 6/2008
- 800141, 1998-2004 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  6/1998; 6/2000; 6/2003; 6/2004
- 800142, 1997-2006 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  6/1997; 6/1998; 6/1999; 6/2000; 6/2001; 6/2004; 6/2006
- 800142, 1995-2000 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  7/1995 - 6/2000
- 800143, 1998-2003 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  6/1998; 6/2002; 6/2003 (1-year extension)
- 800144, 1998-2003 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  12/1998; 12/31/2003
- 800145, 1998-2008 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  6/1998; 6/2000; 6/2002; 6/2005; 6/2008
- 800147, 1994-2003 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  6/1994; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2003
- 800148, 1994-1997 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  9/1994 - 8/1997
- 800148, 1997-2006 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  8/1997; 8/2000; 8/2003; 8/2006
- 800154, 1978-2003 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  6/1978; 6/1981; 6/1985; 6/1988; 6/1991; 6/1993; 6/1996; 6/2003
- 800155, 1999-2003 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  6/30/1999 - 6/30/2003
- 800162, 1997-2005 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2005
- 800163, 1997-2005 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- 800164, 1996-2004 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  11/1997; 11/1996; 11/2001; 11/2004
- 800165, 1995-2003 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2003
- 800166, 1997-2003 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  9/1997; 9/2000; 9/2003
- 800167, 1999-2003 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  6/1999; 6/2003
- 800171, 2003-2007 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  7/2003; 7/2007
- 800171, 1988-1995 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  7/1988 - 7/1995
- 800175, 1997-2007 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2007; 6/2002; 6/2005
- 800172, 1981-2003 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  3/1981; 3/1985; 3/1995; 3/1999; 3/2003
- 800176, 1998-2000 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  6/1998; 6/2000
- 800183, 1995-2005 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  6/1995; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2005
- 800192, 1995-2006 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2006
- 800193, 1989-2007 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  6/1989; 6/1992; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800194, 1999-2007 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800199, 1997-2006 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  2/1997; 2/2000; 2/2003; 2/2006
- 800204, 1999-2003 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- 800205, 2000-2003 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  9/2000; 9/2003
- 800206, 2003-2006 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  6/2003; 6/2006
- 800207, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  6/2004
- 800209, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  6/2003
- 800218, 2000-2003 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  6/2000; 6/2003
- 800219, 1989-2005 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  6/1989; 6/1993; 6/1995; 1/1998; 6/30/2003 extended to 6/30/2005
- 800220, 1999-2005 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  12/1999; 12/2001; 6/2005
- 800221, 2000-2006 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  2/2000; 9/2003; 9/2006
- 800228, 1996-2003 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  6/1996; 6/1999; 6/2003
- 800229, 1993-2003 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  6/1993; 6/2000; 6/2003
- 800230, 1995-2005 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- 800232, 1989-1997 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  7/1989 - 6/1997
- 800232, 1999-2007 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- 800234, 1993-1995 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  7/1993 - 6/1995
- 800234, 1995-2005 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2004; 6/2005
- 800241, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- 800242, 1989-2005 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  6/1989; 6/1991; 6/1997; 6/1997+; 6/30/1999; 6/2003; 6/2004; 6/2005
- 800242, 1987-1997 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  7/1987 - 6/1991; 7/1993 - 6/1997
- 800243, 1999-2005 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2005
- 800244, 1997-2005 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  8/1997; 8/2001; 8/2005
- 800245, 1999-2007 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  6/1999; 6/2003 extended to 6/2005; 6/2007
- 800246, 1995-2005 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  6/1995; 6/1997+; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2004; extended; 6/2005
- 800246, 1993-1997 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  7/1993 - 6/1997
- 800248, 1999-2005 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2004 extended; 6/2005
- 800248, 1993-2007 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  7/1993 - 6/1996
- 800249, 1993-2003 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  6/1993; 6/1995; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2003
- 800250, 2000-2003 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  12/2000 - 12/2003
- 800250, 2000-2003 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  12/2000; 12/2003
- 800252, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- 800252, 1999-2003 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- 800253, 1991-1997 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  7/1991 - 6/1997
- 800253, 1994-2008 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  6/1994; 6/1997; 6/2000; 6/2004; 6/2008
- 800255, 1995-2002 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 10/2002
- 800258, 1991-2007 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  6/1991; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800260, 1999-2003 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  8/1999; 8/2000; 8/2003
- 800261, 1998-2003 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  6/1998; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800262, 2000-2005 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  6/2000; 6/2003; 6/2004; 6/2005
- 800262, 1998-2001 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  7/1998 - 6/2001
- 800264, 1995-2005 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2005
- 800265, 2002-2004 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  8/2002; 9/2004
- 800266, 2000-2006 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  8/2000; 4/2003; 6/2006
- 800267, 1997-2003 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800268, 2001-2004 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  6/2001; 6/2004
- 800270, 1995-2003 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800272, 1994-2004 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2004
- 800273, 1992-2007 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  6/1992; 6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800277, 1997-2003 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 1/2003
- 800278, 2001-2007 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800279, 1998-2004 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- 800281, 1996-2002 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  6/1996; 6/1999; 6/2002
- 800282, 2001-2006 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  6/2001; 6/2004; 12/2006
- 800283, 1999-2005 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- 800286, 2000-2003 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  11/2000; 5/2003
- 800287, 1999-2005 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2002; 6/2003; 6/2005
- 800287, 1997-2001 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  12/1997 - 6/2001
- 800288, 2005-2011 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  10/2005; 10/2011
- 800289, 2004-2006 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  3/2004; 3/2006
- 800293, 1998-2004 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  6/1998; 6/2000; 6/2004
- 800294, 1998-2004 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- 800295, 1998-1999 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  7/1998 - 6/1999
- 800295, 2001-2006 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  7/2001; 7/2003; 7/2006
- 800296, 1997-2007 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  9/1997; 9/2002; 9/2003; 9/2007
- 800297, 1995-2007 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  3/1995; 3/1999; 3/2003; 3/2007
- 800298, 1995-2003 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- 800299, 1993-2003 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  6/1993; 6/1994 (memo); 6/1999; 6/2003
- 800303, 1997-2005 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- 800303, 2005-2007 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- 800304, 1999-2007 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- 800306, 1995-2003 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- 800307, 1999-2007 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- 800309, 1999-2003 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- 800310, 1994-2005 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  6/1994; 6/1999; 6/2002; 6/2005
- 800311, 1991-2003 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  7/1991; 7/1998; 6/2001; 1/2003
- 800313, 1998-2008 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  6/1998; 6/2001; 6/2005; 6/2008
- 800315, 1996-2006 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  6/1996; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2006
- 800316, 1997-2008 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  6/1997; 6/2000; 6/2004; 6/2008
- 800316, 1994-1997 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  7/1994 - 6/1997
- 800317, 1993-2006 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  6/1993; 6/1996; 6/1999; 6/2003; 6/2006
- 800325, 1995-2007 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- 800326, 1999-2005 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- 800327, 1999-2005 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- 800328, 1999-2005 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- 800329, 1994-1997 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- 800329, 1997-2006 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  6/1997; 6/1999; 12/2002; 6/2004; 12/2006
- 800331, 1985-1987 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  July 1 1985 - June 30 1987
- 800334, 2003-2007 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  6/2003; 6/2007
- 800334, 1989-1993 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  7/1989 - 6/1993
- 800335, 1983-2001 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  6/1983; 6/1985; 6/1987; 6/1990; 6/1992; 6/1995; 6/1998; 6/2001
- 800336, 2003-2006 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- 800340, 1999-2007 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2005; 6/2007
- 800345, 1997-2008 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  6/1997; 6/2000; 6/2001; 6/2004; 6/2008
- 800345, 1994-1997 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- 800346, 1995-2004 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  12/1995; 12/1998; 12/2001; 12/2004
- 800348, 1995-2004 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- 800349, 1997-2003 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  1/1997; 6/1999; 6/2003
- 800350, 1993-2003 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  6/1993; 6/1996; 6/2003
- 800352, 1991-2003 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  6/1991; 6/1995; 7/2001; 7/2003
- 800353, 1995-2003 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  6/1995; 7/2001; 7/2003
- 800354, 1995-2003 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- 800355, 1995-2003 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 7/2001; 7/2003
- 800356, 1995-2003 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- 800357, 1995-2006 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 7/2001; 6/2006
- 800358, 1996-2001 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  12/1996; 12/1998; 12/2001
- 800358, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  12/2004
- 800359, 1998-2004 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  12/1998; 12/2001; 12/2004
- 800360, 1996-2003 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  6/1996; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800361, 1999-2003 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  6/1999; 6/2001; 7/2003
- 800362, 1988-2003 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  6/1988; 6/1995; 6/1995; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800363, 1995-2006 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  6/1995; 6/1997; 6/1999; 7/2001; 7/2006
- 800364, 1995-2003 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  6/1995; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800365, 1995-2003 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  6/1995; 6/1999; 6/2001; 4/2003
- 800366, 1993-2001 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  9/1993; 9/1996; 9/1999; 9/2001
- 800368, 1995-2006 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  6/1995; 6/1998; 6/1999; 6/2006
- 800369, 2002-2003 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  January 31 2002 - July 2 2003
- 800370, 2000-2006 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  3/2000; 3/2003; 3/2006
- 800371, 1993-2003 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  6/1993; 6/1995; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003
- 800372, 1992-2005 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  8/1992; 8/1993; 8/1999; 6/2003; 6/2005
- 800374, 1993-1998 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  6/1993; 6/1997; 6/1998 (extended one year)
- 800378, 1997-2007 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800379, 1997-2005 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- 800380, 1994-2004 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  9/1994; 3/1998; 6/2001; 6/2004
- 800381, 2002-2005 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  May 7 2002 - February 1 2005
- 800381, 1993-2005 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  2/1993; 2/1999; 2/2002; 2/2005
- 800382, 1988-1994 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  7/1988 - 6/1994
- 800382, 1994-2006 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  6/1994; 6/1999; 6/2002; 6/2006
- 800386, 1994-2000 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  October 1 1994 - September 30 2000
- 800386, 2000-2003 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  October 1 2000 - September 30 2003; October 1 2000 - September 30 2003
- 800387, 2001-2004 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  April 11 2001 - June 30 2004
- 800387, 1994-2004 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  June 3 1994 - May 31 1997; December 3 1997 - June 30 2000; April 11 2001 - June 30 2004
- 800388, 1993-2003 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  August 20 1993 - August 26 1999; August 27 1999 - August 28 2003
- 800389, 1997-2007 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  April 8 2000 - June 30 2001; December 18 1997 - June 30 1999; January 24 2004 - June 30 2005; June 30 2007
- 800390, 1994-2005 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  July 1 2002 - June 30 2005; July 1 1999 - June 30 2002; July 1 1996 - June 30 1999; July 1 1994 - June 30 1996
- 800391, 1995-2001 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  Jul1 1 1995 - June 30 1998; 8/24/1992 - 6/30/1993; July 1 1998 - June 30 2001
- 800392, 1989-2006 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  July 1 2002- June 30 2006; July 1 1994 - June 30 1999; July 1 1999 - June 30 2002; June 30 1989 - June 30 1994
- 800393, 1992-2006 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  1994 - 1997; 1992 - 1994; 1997-2000; 2003-2006
- 800395, 1993-2001 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  July 1 1993; June 30 1997; July 1 1997 - June 30 2001
- 800397, 1992-2006 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  1992 - 1994; 1994-1997; 1997-2000; 2003-2006
- 800398, 1991-2003 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  3/31/2003; April 1 1994 - March 31 1997; April 1 1997 - March 31 2000; April 1 1991 - March 31 1994
- 800399, 2005-2008 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  5/15/2005; 5/2008
- 800400, 1991-2007 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  3/1991; 3/1995; 3/1999; 3/1999; 3/2003; 3/2007
- 800401, 1996-2005 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  6/1996; 6/1997; 6/2002; 6/2005
- 800402, 1991-2003 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  4/1991; 4/1995; 4/1999; 4/2003
- 800403, 1991-2003 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  4/1991; 4/1995; 4/1999; 3/2003
- 800406, 1995-2007 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  6/1995; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003; 6/2007
- 800407, 1992-2004 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  1992-1994; October 1 2001 - September 30 2004; July 1 1998 - June 30 2000; July 1 1996 - June 30 1998; July 1 2000 - June 30 2002
- 800411, 1996-2005 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  9/1996; 9/1999; 9/2001; 9/2002; 9/2005
- 800412, 1993-2004 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  July 1 1995 - June 30 1999; 9/7/1993; July 1 1999 - June 30 2004
- 800413, 1997-2005 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  July 1 2003 - June 30 2005; 6/30/2003; July 1 1997 - June 30 1999; July 1 1999 - June 30 2001
- 800414, 1995-2007 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  6/1995; 6/1997; 6/1999; 6/2001; 6/2003 - 6/30/2005; 6/2007
- 800415, 1988-1999 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  January 1 1997 - December 31 1999; July 1 1992 - June 30 1995; July 1 1988 - June 30 1990
- 800416, 1994-1999 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  January 16 1997 - July 1 1999; 1994-1995; 6/30/1995
- 800417, 1993-2003 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  July 1 1995 - June 30 1997; July 1 1997 - June 30 1999; July 1 1993 - June 30 1995; July 1 2001 - June 30 2003; July 1 1999 - June 30 2001; July 1 1999 - June 30 2001
- 800419, 1999-2005 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- 800422, 1997-2005 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  11/1997; 11/1999; 11/2002; 11/2005
- 800423, 1994-2002 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  October 1 1998 - September 30 2002; 10/1/1994 - 9/30/1998
- 800424, 1996-2003 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  July 1 2001 - June 30 2003; July 1 1996 - June 30 2001
- 800425, 1997-2003 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  July 1 2001 - June 30 2003; July 1 1999 - June 30 2001; July 1 1997 - June 30 1999
- 800427, 1994-2003 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  July 1 2000 - June 30 2003; July 1 1997 - June 30 2000; July 7 1994 - June 30 1997; August 4 1995
- 800428, 1995-2003 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  July 1 1999 - June 30 2001; July 1 2001 - June 30 2003; July 1 1995 - June 30 1999
- 800429, 1994-2005 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  7/1/2003 - 6/30/2005; 6/30/2003; July 1 1998 - June 30 2001; 1994-1997
- 800430, 1994-2003 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  July 1 2000 - June 30 2003; July 1 1997 - June 30 2000; May 1 1994 - April 30 1996